Guide to the Prometheus Research Library collection on Left Labor Caucuses TAM.192
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Prometheus Research Library Collection on Left Labor Caucuses
1966-1995
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Prometheus Research Library
Kartsen, Diana B.
TAM.192
8.5 Linear Feet in eight record cartons and one manuscript box.
This collection principally consists of printed ephemera from left rank and file caucuses within labor unions in the United States and other Anglophone countries from the late 1960s through the early 1990s. Labor unions most prominently represented are the United Automobile Workers (aka the International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), the United Steel Workers of America, the International Longshoremen's and Warhousemen's Union, the Communications Workers of America, the National Maritime Union, and the American Federation of Teachers.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Diana B. Kartsen on behalf of Prometheus Research Library (New York) in 1997. The accession number associated with this gift is 1997.061.
Arrangement
Organized into two series: I, Processed Materials (arranged alphabetically); II, Unprocessed Materials.
Historical/Biographical Note
The 1970s and 1980s saw widespread deindustrialization and a worsening political and legal climate for organized labor in the United States. In response to these conditions, and to the perceived inadequacy of union leaders' responses to these challenges, rank and file caucuses arose in many unions and localities. A large role was played by former student activists of the New Left, many of whom had found their way into numerous small and often short-lived communist, socialist, Trotskyist and Maoist organizations.
The Prometheus Research Library assembled and donated this collection. The Prometheus Research Library is a research facility for Marxist studies and the central reference archive of the Spartacist League of the U.S. The Spartacist League of the U.S. is a Trotskyist organization and section of the International Communist League (Fourth International). The Prometheus Research Library's collection is centered upon the work and interests of the American Communist and Trotskyist movements.
Related Archival Materials
Related collections at Tamiment include Communications Workers of America Records (WAG 124), Communications Workers of America Printed Ephemera Collection (PE 023), Communications Workers of America Oral History Collection (OH 026), and National Maritime Union of America Printed Ephemera Collection (PE 008).
Collections relating to the International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America and its locals, including Local 600, can be found at the Walter P. Reuther Library at Wayne State University. Materials related to the United Steelworkers of America can be found in the United Steelworkers of America Archives at Pennsylvania State University.
Scope and Contents
This collection principally consists of printed ephemera from left rank and file caucuses within labor unions in the United States and other Anglophone countries from the late 1960s through the early 1990s. Labor unions most prominently represented are the United Automobile Workers (aka the International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), the United Steelworkers of America, the International Longshoremen's and Warhousemen's Union, the Communications Workers of America, the National Maritime Union, and the American Federation of Teachers. Strongly represented locals include UAW Local 600 (Dearborn, Michigan), UAW Local 1364 (Fremont, California), and ILWU Local 6 (Bay Area). There are also materials from some radical political parties that play a leading role in this activity, and from labor organizations they founded, as well as subject files.
Separated Materials
One half linear foot of official labor union, U.S. Department of Labor, and outside left publications have been separated to the library's serial and pamphlet holdings.
Labor unions and communism -- United States.; Labor union members |z United States.; Labor unions |z United States |y 1970-1990.; Deindustrialization |z United States.; Labor union democracy |z United States.; Labor movement |z Canada.; Canada.; Labor movement |z Michigan.; Trotskyists -- United States.; Labor movement -- United States.; Detroit (Mich.); Labor movement |z California.; New Left -- United States.; Spartacist League of the U.S.; International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union; Communications Workers of America; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Ford Local 600; American Federation of Teachers; National Maritime Union of America; United Steelworkers of America; Kartsen, Diana B.
- Processed Materials, 1968-1989; 1
  - AESCME - Opposition Group, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Auto, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Auto Company Material, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AWUF (RCP), 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Buffalo Steel, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - CLUW Conf. ORO on CLUW, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - CWA Bellwringer, Yellow Pages, IS SF Opposition, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - CWA Convention 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CWA Convention 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - CWA Convention 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - CWA Convention 1979, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CWA - Final Warning NYC, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - CWA - Local 4050, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - CWA - Local 11501, 1978-1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - CWA - Local Officials 9415, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - CWA - Local Officials 9490, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - CWA - Militant Caucus, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - CWA - National Official, 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - CWA - New York Area Misc, 1971-1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - CWA - 1101 Officials, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - CWA - United Action NYC, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Detroit Area Misc Left & Opposition, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Dist. 31 Conference, June 1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Facing Reality, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - ILWU 21st Convention 1975 Vancouver BC (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - ILWU #1, 1969-1982 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - ILWU Opppositions, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - ILWU - Wavehouse Local 6, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - INCAR (PL), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Labour Black League, 1968-1982 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Labour Black League (affiliated with Spartacist League), 1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Local 1364, Brotherhood Caucus 1974, Official (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Local Elections USWA 1975 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Local 906 (UAW) Elections 1977, 1968-1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Local 10 ILWU - Longstone General, 1973-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Local 600 Klan Foreman, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Local 1364, Opposition Groups 1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Longshore Militant & LM/WM, 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Newspapers, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - NMC Militant Action, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - NBCC Convention - 5th Annual 1977 National Black Coalition Communication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - NMU Leaflets, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Officials CWA NY Area, 1972-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Partisan Defense Committee, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Phone Misc Oppositions, 1972-1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Postal, 1971-1989 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Postal Workers, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Runnels/ Short Work Week Committee, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Sadlowski Campaign Material 1976-1977, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Sadlowski Evett Campaign Dist. 31, 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Steel Co Pubs, 1973-1977 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Steel Industry Research #1, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Steel Industry Research #2, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Steel Opposition CP, 1973-1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Steel Organization - WAM, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Steel Workers, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Teamsters, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Turf - Teamsters, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - TWU, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - TWU - Racist Murder, Willy Turfs, 1982-1989 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - UAW, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - UAW - Arab Workers Caucus - General, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - UAW - Auto Workers Action Caucus (C. P.), 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - UAW - Buffalo - General, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - UAW - Coalition for good conduct, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - UAW - 25th Constitutional Convention 1979, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - UAW Contract 1979 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - UAW Contract 1979 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - UAW Convention, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - UAW Convention, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - UAW Convention, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - UAW Convention (Bargaining), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - UAW Convention Minutes, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - UAW Detroit 1975 Local Elections (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - UAW ISTC, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - UAW L. 1364 Convention Elections/ Resolutions, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - UAW L. 1364 Convention Elections 1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - UAW L. 1364 Convention Elections 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - UAW L. 1364 General/Oppositions through '74, 1967-1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - UAW Local 961 (Jordan Simms), 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - UAW Local Misc. - General, 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - UAW Local 906, Official 1972-1974, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - UAW L. 1364 Official Bun, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - UAW Local 1364 - Official & Brotherhood (through '73), 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - UAW L. 906 Official 1975 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - UAW L. 906 Official 1976, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - UAW L. 1364 (OL) 1975 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - UAW L. 1364 (OL), 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - UAW L. 906 - Opposition Groups 1975, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - UAW Local 906 - Opposition Groups ('72-'74), 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - UAW L. 1364 Other Oppositions, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - UAW L. 1364 RCP 1974, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - UAW L. 1364 RCP, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - UAW L. 1364 RCP, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - UAW L. 906, United Black Workers, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - UAW Misc. International Union, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - UAW 1974 National Ford Council (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - UAW NY/NJ area Opposition Groups, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - UAW Other Detroit Locals 1977 Elections (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - UAW - Paul Schrade, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - UAW Production Workers Conference, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - UAW Revolutionary Auto-workers Caucus (RSL), 1973-1977 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - UAW RUMS (CLP), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - UAW Skilled Trades Conference, Feb 1979 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - UAW Skilled Trades, General, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - UAW - 1364 South Africa Demo, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - UAW - WAM, 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - UAW: Women; Sex Discrimination & CLUW, 1965-1972 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - UE Local 107, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - UE L26Z Cambion Strike, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - UFW Convention, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - UFW General, 1969-1977 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - UMWA - Yablonsky-Miller Opp., 1969-1973 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - UNC, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Unemployed Council (CLP), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Unions & Social Defense, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - United National Caucus, 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - United National Caucus, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - United National Caucus, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - USW, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - USWA, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - USWA Basic documents, 1966-1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - USWA Convention 1974 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - USWA Convention 1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - USWA Convention September 1978 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - USWA Crisis in Steel Case, Gary, Ind., 13th November '77, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - USWA District 31 Annual Conference 15th October 1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - USWA District 31 Misc OMOS, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - USWA - General, 1949-1975 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - USWA - Houston: Hughes Tool, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - USWA - Local 1014 (Gary) Misc OROS, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - USWA Misc - Local Bureaucracies, 1973-1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - USWA Misc OMOS, 1974-1979 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - USWA - Newport News, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - USWA Right to Strike cont 17-18 August '74 (Dist 31), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - UWOC (RCP), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - WAM, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Warehouse Militant & Misc Leaflets, 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - World Auto Conference/IMF, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Unprocessed Materials
  - CWA: Bay Area, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Labor Notes: Conference, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Hospital Workers: San Francisco, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - California: Committee for Better Working Conditions, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Workmen's Committee, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Don't Mourn, ORGANIZE!, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - ILWU, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - ILWU, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - UMW, 1978-1984 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Trade Union Action and Democracy, circa 1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - USWA, 1980-1992 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Fighting Back, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - BRAC (Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks), undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - UMWA, 1978-1989 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - International Socialists, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Machinists, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - UAW Local 6, undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - National Union of Mineworkers (UK), circa 1985 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Detroit, undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - ILWU, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - CWA: Militant Action Caucus, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - UAW, 1976-1982 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - General Rank and File, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Farm Workers, undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - California, 1969-1975 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Postal Workers, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - General Rank and File, undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - New York, circa 1970-1980 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Newark Teachers Union, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - AFSCME, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - OCAW (Oil, Cehmical and Atomic Workers International Union), 1982-1989 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - UAW, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - NMU, 1975-1980 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Workers Education Center, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - NMU Convention, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Labor Notes, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Save Dodge Main, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Association for Union Democracy, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Log: Official Publication of the Seafarers International Union Atlantic, Gulf, Lakes and Inland Waters District, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - West Coast Sailors, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - U.S. Department of Labor, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - UE (United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America), undated (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - UAW Local 600, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - AFL-CIO, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - TDU, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - The Committee for New Leadership, undated (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - UAW, undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Transit Workers, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Labor - General, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Mountain Life and Work, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Workers' Advocate, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Transit Workers, undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Voice of Rank and File in Transportation, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - ILWU, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - California: General, circa 1970-1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - New York: General, circa 1970-1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Texas Socialist Workers Campaign, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Safe Working Environments for Public Employees, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Spartacist, circa 1970-1985 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - CWA, circa 1970-1985 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - NMU, circa 1970-1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - UAW, circa 1970-1985 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - USWA, circa 1970-1985 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - CWA, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Local 732, circa 1980 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - AFSCME, undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - General Press, circa 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Canadian Labour Congress, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Canadian Labour Congress, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - American Merchant Marine Conference, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - World Magazine, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - On the Line, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Strike at UC, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Race Relations News (South Africa), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Fighting Back, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - National Rank-and-File Conference, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Labor Black Struggle League, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Greater New York Area Labor Support Committee, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Metal Trades Council, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - David Duke, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Reality (South Africa), 1977 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - USWA, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - LCUC - Bureaucrats, circa 1970-1985 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - (Australia) Amalgamated Metal Workers Union, circa 1970-1985 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Spartacist League of Australia and New Zealand, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Democratic National Convention - Delegates and Endorsements, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - South Africa Instute of Race Relations, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - British Miners Solidarity Rally, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Solidaritat, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - CWA, circa 1970-1980 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - UMWA Miners Right to Strike Committee, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Bandwagon Magazine (South Africa), 1975 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Our Own, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Black People's Convention, circa 1970-1985 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Misc. ORO and Frontgroup Union Leaflets, circa 1970-1980 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Philadelphia Workers Organizing Committee, undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - CWA, 1972-1983 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - ILWU, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - AFT and Teachers - General, circa 1970-1975 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - CWA - Militant Action Caucus, circa 1970-1985 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - CWA - Militant Action Caucus, circa 1970-1980 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - AFT 1974 Convention: Officials (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - AFT 1974 Convention Teacher Unity (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - AFT 1977 National Convention (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - AFT 1974 Convention Black Caucus (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - AFT ORO-OMO (Misc.), circa 1970-1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - AFT 1974 Convention Misc. ORO/OMOs (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Economics Research Files, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Labor Black League for Social Defense, circa 1983-1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Hormel, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Union Women's Alliance to Gain Equality, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Teamsters, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - NMU, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - UAW Local 600 (Communist Party Supported), circa 1970-1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - UAW Local 600, PL Supported, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - UAW, Local 600, Time to Unite (RCP Supported), 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - UAW Local 600 Supported by CLP, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - UAW Local 600 Misc. Oppositions, undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Local 600, Misc. Oppositions, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - UAW Local 600 Official, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - UAW Local 600 Official, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - UAW, Local 212 (MACK) General, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - UAW Local 216 (LA) - Southgate, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - UAW Local 303 General (Toronto), 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - UAW Local 422 (Framingham), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Local 600 CMDUAW, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - UAW Local 600 Elections, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - UAW Local 600 Spark, 1974-1980 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - UAW Dodge Local 140 Opposition Groups, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - UAW Local 140 Dodge Truck Wildcat, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Local 140 Oppositions, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - UAW Local 140, Workers Unity (Supported by RCP), 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - UAW Local 140 (Supported by OL), 1977 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - UAW Local 600 Official, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - UAW Local 600 Elections Convention, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - UAW Local 600 Official, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - UAW Local 600 Supported Group, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - UAW Local 600 DAP, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - UAW Local 600 Elections, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Local 700 (Oraville) SL Supported, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - UAW Local 140 (Dodge Truck) Spark, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - UAW Local 6 Elections, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - UAW Local 6 Rank and File Coalition, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - UAW Local 7 (Jefferson) Official, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - UAW Local 7 (Supported by IS), 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - UAW Local 7 Other Left Oppositions, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - UAW Local 15, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - UAW Local 22, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - UAW Local 51 (Lynch Rd) General, 1973-1977 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - UAW Local 140 (Dodge Truck) Official, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - UAW Local 140 (Supported by CLP), 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - UAW Local 6 Official, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - UAW Local 6 Elections, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - UAW Local 6 Elections, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - UAW Local 6 Official, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - UAW Local 6 Official/General, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - UAW Local 6 Official, General, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - UAW Local 3 (Dodge Main) Official, 1974-1977 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - UAW Local 3 Spark, 1974-1979 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - UAW Local 3 Strike back UNC Supported by IS, circa 1974 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - UAW Local 3, Other Oppositions, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - UAW Local 6 (IS Supported), circa 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - UAW, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - 1979 Strike Local 6/Ag Imp (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - NMU, 1979-1982 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - National UAW Ford Council, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - ILWU, 1978-1984 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - UAW, circa 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - UAW, circa 1975-1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - ILWU, 1976-1983 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - ILWU, circa 1975-1985 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - UAW, 1974-1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - AFT and UFT, 1973-1993 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - BTU, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - CWA, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - UAW, circa 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - ILWU, circa 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - UAW Local 600, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - UAW Local 600: Rouge Militant, 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - UAW District 65: Workers' Voice (Village Voice), 1982 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - UAW Militant Caucuses, 1970-1983 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - UAW Local 600: Rouge Militant, 1979-1983 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - UAW, 1974-1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - UAW, circa 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - ILWU Local 6, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - ILWU Local 10, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - ILWU, 1974-1979 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - ILWU Convention, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - ILWU Local 6, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - ILWU Local 6, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - ILWU Local 6, circa 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - ILWU: Warehouse Victory, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - ILWU, circa 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - ILWU Vancouver, circa 1970-1980 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - ILWU Local 10, circa 1968-1974 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - UMWA, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - UMWA 1976 Convention (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - AFSCME Local 2070, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - ILWU Historical, 1971-1979 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Steel Legal Cases, circa 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Hospital Workers, 1974-1985 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - New York Committee for Trade Union Action and Democracy, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Stop Senate 1 Bill, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 37)